我出价35
So I'm thinking 35.
对我来说高了点
Seems high to me.
这种质量卖这个价很公平了
That's a fair price for quality like this.
我出30
I'll give you 30.
怎么了  我以为你在开玩笑
What? I thought you were joking.
我在和谁做生意  艾迪
Who am I dealing with here, Eddie?
是你还是他
Him or you?
别紧张  米奇
Mickey, relax.
这样吧  如果能和戈尔斯基合作
Now, If things move forward with Gorski,
让我们进入费城做生意
He lets us into philly,
到时候我就给你优惠
Then maybe I cut you a break.
现在就得给我优惠
You cut me a break now,
不然你没机会见到戈尔斯基
Or maybe you don't get with Gorski.
马可
Marco...
我还以为咱俩都谈好了
I thought we had an understanding.
别做傻事  汤米  把枪放下
Tommy, don't be stupid. Put the gun down.
他已经给你留足面子了
First, he shows you some respect.
听从你老板的吩咐
Hey, You just-- just listen to your boss,
好吗  傻瓜
All right, moron?
闭嘴
You shut up!
哥们  放松
Just relax, buddy.
天
Oh, god!
你他妈干嘛呢
What the hell were you thinking?
我没射中他  确定吗
I didn't shoot him! Are you sure?
你看  他脸朝下摔倒在地上
Look at him. He's face-down on the pavement!
我伤到自己的脚了
I nailed myself in the foot!
天
God!
他看起来没中弹
I--I don't think he's hit.
那是怎么回事
Then what happened?
我们赶紧走
Let's get outta here!
米奇  醒醒
Come on, Mickey, wake up.
米奇  醒一醒
Mickey! Wake up!
手术结束了吧
We almost done here?
你的前额已经清理干净
Assuming you did this shaving your forehead...
下一步
Okay, then.
我已经约好了脑部扫描
I'm ordering a head C.T.
不用了  我既不头疼也不头晕
No, I don't have a headache. I'm not dizzy.
艾迪  我得回去了
Eddie, I gotta get back.
你得留下来
You gotta stay here.
明天再收拾马可那边的烂摊子
We'll straighten out that mess with Marco tomorrow.
让医生做完检查
Let the doc do his job.
其实  为你缝合
Actually, stitching you up
本该是急诊室医生的职责
Is really the E.R. Doc's job.
是啊
Yeah.
等不及了
Too long of a wait.
何况外科那边还有好多条子
Yeah. Also, a lot of cops in the E.R.
倒不是说你怕这个
Not that you care about that.
怎么受的伤
So how did this happen?
好吧  这是个傻问题
Yeah, you're right. That was a stupid question.
因为答案很明显
'cause the answer's kind of obvious.
手上没有擦伤
No scrapes on your hands
意味着摔倒时你没有反抗
Means you didn't try to break your fall.
也就是说倒下时
Means either out cold
你已经完全失去意识或方向感了
Or totally disoriented when you went down.
除了这里没有别的外伤
No sign of trauma other than the cut
意味着没人打过你的头
Means no one hit you in the head.
夹克袖子上的火药味
Powder burn on your jacket sleeve
意味着有人开枪了
Means someone shot a gun.
好了  艾迪  我们走吧
All right, Eddie. Come on, let's go.
我不关心你们干什么勾当
I don't care what you guys are into.
不过如果不查出病因
If you don't get this checked out,
你还会发病的
It'll happen again.
在什么情况下
Whoa. What will?
像这样
This.
酷
Cool.
32岁男性
32-year-old man,
突然出现强噪音所致的眩晕
Recently developed loud-noise-induced vertigo.
脑部扫描没有问题
C.T. Was clean.
没有内出血和浮肿
No internal bleeding, no edema.
所有文件都在这里
Everything else is in the file.
离婚时卡梅隆带走了你的秀发吗
Cameron get your hair in the divorce?
三年前他后背受过伤
This guy strained his back three years ago.
就这些了
And that's it.
其他页都是空白
All the rest of these pages are blank.
没错  他嘴很严
Yes, he won't tell us anything.
作为一个毒贩子  这可以理解
Understandable, since he's a drug dealer.
这个病人危险而且有所隐瞒
So he's dangerous and withholding,
对你来说太有诱惑力了
Which you find irresistible.
不过这种人从来不打电话的
But guys like that, they never call.
他真说过自己是毒贩子吗
He actually said he was a drug dealer?
他没说
Not out loud.
不过戴着纯金的百达翡丽
But he was wearing a solid gold patek philippe.
他的朋友则是劳力士
His friend had a rolex.
却用着便宜的预付费手机
But their phones were prepaid burners,
以便联络完就扔掉
So they can toss 'em as soon as they're done.
这家伙是不是毒贩子都不重要
It doesn't matter if this guy's a drug dealer or not.
噪音引发眩晕症状表明耳部或脑部有问题
Noise-induced vertigo means ear or brain.
脑部扫描没问题
Head C.T. was clean,
我猜测是听觉神经瘤
So I'm thinking acoustic neuroma.
需要做听性脑干反应测试听力
We need to do an A.B.R. To test his hearing.
听觉神经瘤符合症状
Acoustic neuroma fits.
利多卡因中毒也说得通
So does lidocaine toxicity.
或者苯坐卡因  就看他用什么混可卡因
Or benzocaine--depends what he's cutting the coke with.
他不仅是个毒贩子
So now he's not just a drug dealer,
还是个卖可卡因的
He's a cocaine dealer.
这人看起来精力充沛
He seemed peppy.
你们给耳朵做检查
You test his ears.
我去检测一下可卡因
I'm gonna go test his cocaine.
你真以为这些人受你蛊惑
You think this guy's just gonna hand over
会乖乖的交出
A briefcase full of illegal drugs
手里的非法药物吗
Because you ask nicely?
希望不是
I hope not.
这边最好的咖啡店是吉娜
So the best coffee's at Geena's,
最好的批萨则是吉诺家
And the best pizza is at Gino's.
没错  千万别搞混了
Yeah, And don't mix those up,
因为Gino的咖啡难喝的要死
Because the coffee at Gino's could kill ya.
那街角的干洗机怎么样
And how's the drycleaner on the corner?
两个街区外有环保清洗机
Go two blocks over to eco-clean.
街角那台
The one on the corner
曾经绞碎了我男友的衬衫
Used to shred all my boyfriend's shirts.
这样啊
Good to know.
回想起来  真该感谢那些人
In retrospect, I should really thank those cleaners.
我们分手了
We broke up.
我该走了  有什么需要打听的
This is my stop. So if you have any more questions
生活信息  随时来找我
About the neighborhood, I'm your girl.
最好的寿司店在哪
Uh, favorite sushi place.
我们可以吃个晚饭
Maybe we could get dinner sometime.
当然  你得带着那个帅哥
Sure...If you promise to bring that good-looking guy
拄拐那个
With the cane.
你是指豪斯吗
You mean House?
你男友叫豪斯吗
Your boyfriend's name is House?
他不是我男友
H-he's not my boyfriend.
抱歉  说漏了
Heh, I'm sorry.
你们怎么称呼彼此
Wh-what do you call each other?
丈夫  伴侣
Husband? Partner?
爱人
Lover?
我们不是同性恋
We're not gay.
真的吗
Seriously?
你会听到一组咔哒声和嘶嘶声
You're gonna hear a series of clicks and hisses.
传感器会记录下传导至听觉神经
Sensors measure electronic activity
脑电波活动状况
To your auditory nerve.
要检查多长时间
How long is this gonna take?
一个或一个半小时
An hour, maybe an hour and a half.
或者你带着耳朵里的肿瘤出院
Or you could walk away with a tumor in your ear.
这家伙可能急着火拼去
Guy's probably late to a stabbing.
阻抗正常
Impedances look good.
开始以每秒13下50分贝检测
Starting at 13 clicks per second at 50 decibels.
看看这个
Check this out.
13的中间名是博勒加德
13's middle name is beauregard?
第三波潜伏期值为3.8
Wave three latency is 3.8.
轻微滞后  不过没大问题
Slightly delayed, but nothing significant.
你就注意到那个了吗
That's what sticks out to you?
豪斯摆明了耍咱俩
House is clearly screwing with us.
这是伪造的工资单
It's a fake paystub.
我觉得像真的
Looks real to me.
没理由她挣这么多
There's no way she makes that much money.
我也是这个数
I make that much money.
显然  你没这么多
And...apparently, you don't.
我想嗑药
I need the drugs.
我们是搞服装生意的
We're in textiles.
我想嗑药
I need the drugs!
这招对杰克·鲍尔[24小时主演]管用
Hmm...works for Jack Bauer.
这有必要吗
Is this really necessary?
大厅里的椅子舒服多了
The chairs in the hall are way more comfortable.
但是不太适合你
But way less genre-appropriate.
这么办吧
Okay, here's the deal.
我想打听点事
I need information.
你可以不告诉我
You have reasons not to give me that information.
要不我强迫你说出来
So either I can force it out of you...
或者你自己说
Or I can't.
我真没什么可说的
I wish I could tell you.
好吧  这样吧
Okay...well, let's work with that.
不提药了  说说你们的服装生意吧
Forget the drugs. Let's talk about textiles.
你们主要生产什么
What's your major product?
是不是以H开头
Is it "H"?
我是指袜子
And by that I mean "Hosiery."
我们主要做
We do more with...
裙裤
Culottes.
是以C开头还是K
Is that with a "C" Or a "K"?
C
"C."
没人想要K了
Nobody wants "K" Anymore.
你的朋友负责剪裁吗
Does your friend cut the fabric
不  他负责销售
No, he's a sales guy.
他肯定是自己动手做裙裤了
Well, he must cut a culotte here and the
没人动过这批裙裤
No one touches the culottes.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
能说句话吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
我正在审嫌疑犯呢
I'm interrogating a suspect.
有话快说
Make it quick.
咱家大楼里每个人都觉得我们是同性恋
Everyone in our building thinks we're gay.
我们都是30岁以上的成人了
We're grown men overge of 30
只不过搬到一起住
Moved in together.
到了维加斯我们就是两头老虎
We're two tigers away n act in vegas.
他们最终会明白的
They'll figure out e straight eventually.
但是我现在就因为这个原因
Eventually is not when I want to go out
没法约3b那位可爱的姑娘
With the cute girl in 3-b.
能给我杯水喝吗
Any chance I could get some water over here?
如果有什么东西
If only there was some way
能让她感觉是这样的话
To communicate that information to her.
难道是  我不知道  声音吗
Perhaps using, I don't know, sounds.
只要嗓音能...
If only the larynx was capable of--
她不相信我
She didn't believe me.
她婉拒了我共进晚餐的邀请
She sidestepped my dinner invite.
一个女人拒绝你
And a woman would only reject you
正因为她担心
Because she's worried
你可能对她不感兴趣
That you might not be interested in her.
我们聊天很开心
We were chatting, having fun.
绝对有爱的火花
There was definitely a spark.
基于她觉得你是基佬
When she thought you were gay.
你确定你哥们儿暗地里...
You sure your friend isn't secretly tr--
什么是裤裙
What is a culotte, anyway?
看上去像裙子的裤子
Pants that hang like a skirt.
就是...
Just...
米奇讨厌那玩意儿
Mickey hates the stuff.
他是少数几个我信任的之一
He's one of the few guys I trust
能让他看着货过夜的人
To watch the product overnight.
他们一小时前带走了他
They took him away an hour ago.
你觉得他没事吗
You think he's okay?
只是个耳朵测试罢了
It's an ear test.
肯定他会活着回来的
Pretty sure he'll live.
瞳孔缩小  心跳剧烈
Pupils are constricted. Pulse is bounding!
导气管准备好了
Airway's clear.
快来个急救车
Need a crash cart in here!
必须测血压
Gotta be his blood pressure.
我们得在他休克前搞定
We need to get it down before he strokes out!
至少我们知道他的耳朵没问题
At least we know his ears are okay.
我们给他用了血管扩张药
We put the patient on vasodilators,
血压稳定下来了
Got his hypertension under control.
他在医院反而症状更严重了
He got worse here at the hospital.
意味着不是犯罪活动让他生病的
Means thug life probably isn't what's making him sick.
意味着我们可以不必当侦探
Which means we can stop the bloodhound gang routine
回头好好做医生了
And go back to being doctors.
但我们一直是医生啊
But we're doctors all the time.
真没劲啊
It's so boring.
好吧
Fine.
可能是病态窦房结综合征
Could be sick sinus syndrome.
胸腔没有疼痛  呼吸困难
No chest pain, shortness of breath.
是脑动脉瘤导致了多囊性肾病吗
Brain aneurysm secondary to polycystic kidney disease?
做了常规尿检
Normal urinalysis.
表明肾部没问题
Kidney's impalpable.
那...  是块新表吗
Is...that a new watch?
我觉得该对自己好一点
Thought I'd give myself a little treat.
如果不是他脑部的问题
What if it's not his brain,
那么很可能是到脑部之前的问题
But it's on the way to his brain?
颈动脉狭窄
Carotid stenosis.
给他做颈动脉超声波检查
Get an ultrasound of his carotids.
看看他是否有动脉栓塞
See if his arteries are clogged.
你挣多少钱
How much money do you make?
我要求加薪
I want a raise.
我倒是愿意在
And I will be happy to talk about that
你的下一次评估时讨论此问题...  八月
At your next review... in august.
我知道你给我的钱
I know that you're paying me
比小组里任何一个人都少
Less than everyone else on the team.
我不能谈论其他人的工资
I can't discuss other people's salaries.
你知道的
You know that.
因为他们都知道我赚的比他们少了
Now that they know I'm making less than they are,
他们会轻视我的
They'll never respect me.
那么是谁告诉他们你挣多少钱的呢
And who told them how much you make?
我挣的钱比我管的人
It's not fair for me to make less
都少  这不公平
Than the people I supervise.
薪水不是关乎公平的
Salary isn't about fairness.
而是关乎你能否占据谈判的有利地位
It's about what you can leverage in negotiation.
如果桌上没有一份有竞争力的应聘书的话
Which isn't much without a competing offer on the table.
而我们都知道你没有
And we both know you don't have one.
超声波显示病人颈动脉
Ultrasound showed no narrowing
没有狭窄或栓塞
Or obstruction in the patient's carotid.
现在他担心的是...
Not that he's worried--
他一直问我什么时候可以出院
Keeps asking me when he can leave.
你在他病房装了窃听器吗
You bugged his room?
我们的病人住在
Our patient sleeps in the building
他们窝赃的地方
Where they keep their stash.
终于  他们要说出
Eventually, he'll say something
他们把毒品放到哪里了
That gives away where that is.
而我们也会找到他的病因
And we'll find out what's making him sick.
但我们已经排除了环境因素
But we ruled out environmental causes.
是你排除了环境因素
You ruled out environmental causes.
但你还假装同意了
And you pretended to agree,
所以趁我们把他带出病房时
Just so we'd take him out of his room
你就安装了窃听器
So you could plant the bug.
颈动脉狭窄是个不错的想法
Carotid stenosis was a decent idea.
但更正点的想法
But an even decent-er idea
是他把毒品藏在了他的脂肪细胞里
Is that he's got toxins stored in his fat cells.
他燃烧的每卡热量都让病情更严重
Every calorie he burns makes him sicker.
如果我们要处理毒品超量
If we're going with toxic exposure,
我们应该开始检查出最可能的嫌疑人
We should just start testing for the most likely suspects.
窃听器是个好主意
Bug's a better idea
总比成天瞎做检查的强
Than blindly running tests for days.
告诉他还得几周
Tell him it'll take weeks.
会很快的
It'll be faster.
你说几周是什么意思
What do you mean weeks?
检查需要时间
These tests take time.
因为有很多种致病可能
There are a lot of possibilities.
不  但我  我不能在这待那么久
No, but I--I can't sit here this long.
我有事要处理
I got things I gotta take care of.
如果你是为那些穷学生
If you're worried about all the poor school children
没有毒品而担心
Going without their drugs,
我肯定有人...
I'm sure someone--
我要出院
I wanna be discharged.
我去拿表格
I'll get the forms.
太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
比成天待在实验室强
Beats sitting in a lab all day.
在实验室
In the lab,
很显然极少有被杀的危险
There is significantly less chance of getting killed.
跟得太近了  慢点
You're too close. Slow down.
我们光天化日之下待在一辆车里
We're in a car in broad daylight.
会有什么事
What's gonna happen?
你天真地以为他不会在车里放把枪吗
You honestly think he doesn't have a gun in that car?
他会用那个来射击医生吗
That he's gonna use to shoot doctors?
你就...  离远点
Just...back off.
手表的戏演得不错  顺便说
Hey, well played with the watch, by the way.
从一个朋友那借的
Borrowed it from a friend.
我们要骗他多久
How much longer are we gonna keep lying to him?
直到不好玩了为止
Until it's no longer fun.
我们都觉得他应该变得低调点
We all thought he needed to be taken down a few notches.
所以只是玩玩  不是让事态严重化吗
So we're just having fun, not getting even?
靠
Oh, crap.
会跟丢的
He's gonna get away.
闭嘴
Shut up.
3-b吗
3-b?
你是诺拉  对吗
You're Nora, right?
我室友告诉我说你是我们应该感谢的
My roommate tells me you're the one to thank
那个总是贴纸条通知我们的邻居
For all the tips about the neighborhood.
-格雷格  -很高兴认识你
- Greg. -Nice to meet you.
我听说你以为威尔森和我
I hear you thought that wilson and I
喜欢互相亮剑的
Liked to polish each other's swords.
我说的"剑"  其实应该是"手枪"
And by swords, I mean pistols.
当然他会告诉你的
Of course he told you about that.
别担心
Oh, don't worry.
实际上我很惊讶  这样的事很少发生
Actually, I'm surprised that doesn't happen more often.
我们俩都很直男
We're both straight.
我的...  上帝啊
Oh, my...god.
真漂亮
That is beautiful.
我们终于有一件可以
We finally have the room
彰显房间品质的物件了
To display it the way it deserves.
你能...  你能帮我搬到楼上去吗
Would you--would you help me get this upstairs?
当然
Absolutely.
顺便说  鞋真漂亮
Nice shoes, by the way.
鲁布托牌的吗
Louboutin?
你和卡迪说了吗
You talk to Cuddy?
雷死我了
Shot me down.
那么  现在怎么办
So, uh, what are you gonna do now?
我得等待8月的评估
I'll wait for my review in August.
什么
What?
没什么
Nothing.
是我也会那么做的
That's what I would do.
但我是个懦夫
But I'm a coward.
他朋友15分钟前送他来的
His friend brought him in 15 minutes ago.
体温105华氏摄氏度
Temp's 105.
脉搏纤弱
Pulse is weak and thready.
他一点意识都没有
He's not making any sense.
有很多钱  艾迪
It's too much money, Eddie.
不能成交
That wasn't the deal.
他会没事吗
Is he gonna be okay?
艾迪
Eddie!
我们给他用退烧药和类固醇来退烧
We gave him antipyretics and soft steroids
防止器官损坏
To reduce the fever and prevent organ damage.
他已经不再神志不清了
He's no longer delirious.
病人出院  回来后情况更糟
Patient went out, came back worse than before.
指明我们应该回到环境问题上
Points us back to environmental,
关系到他去过哪
Tied to wherever he went.
不是  福曼去哪里
No, it doesn't. Where's Foreman?
他和卡迪开会呢
He had a meeting with Cuddy.
你说"不是"是什么意思
What do you mean, "No, it doesn't"?
我们没跟上  我的车被甩了
We screwed up the tail. My car was impounded.
确实  好玩  而且毫无意义
True, amusing, and irrelevant.
福曼落入薪水圈套了吗
Foreman fall for the paycheck thing?
是的
Uh, yeah.
祝他好运
Mazel tov.
看好戏很好玩吧
Should be fun to watch.
你觉得不是环境问题吗
You're off environmental?
无论他去哪  时间都不够久
Wherever he went, It wasn't for long enough.
从发烧来看  更像是感染
Add in the fever and infection's way more likely.
而且如果是感染的话
And if it is an infection,
他的症状显示已经入侵大脑了
His symptoms suggest it's moved to his brain.
意味着
Which means...
我们得做个腰椎穿刺
We'll do a lumbar puncture.
下次跟踪车的时候
Next time you're tailing someone,
开两辆车
Take two cars.
你知道我们跟踪你了吗
You knew we were following you?
对不起  我必须甩掉你们
I'm sorry. I had to lose you.
我还有正事要做
I had business to take care of.
对啊  因为你是个商人呢
Right, because you're a businessman.
你知道每星期有多少吸毒者
Do you know how many junkies
因脑部融化而被送进急诊室吗
Come into the e.r. every week with their brains melting?
我打赌更多人因酗酒而切除肝脏
I'll bet there's more drunks with their livers giving out.
我猜一个经营酒类商店的人
A liquor store owner
在这个手术台上  也不会得到尊重
Laying on this table-- I'm guessing he doesn't get attitude.
我刺到骨头了
I hit bone.
他背部的旧伤
His old back injury
一定把椎间盘磨平了
Must have flattened out his discs.
对不起  可是我要再试一遍
Sorry, but I've got to try this again.
-你还好吗  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
一个成年人想颓废一下
An adult wants to get wasted,
为什么每个人都要管他用的是哪种方式
Why is it anybody's business what substance they use?
因为有些方式是违反法律的
Because some of those substances are against the law.
所以你是说问题不在于它是不道德的
So your problem isn't that it's immoral.
问题在于它是违法的
Your problem is that it's illegal.
我也有同样的问题
I got the same problem.
进去了
I'm in.
看他的心率
Look at his heart rate.
正常啊
It's normal.
我知道
I know.
我今早碰见诺拉了
I ran into Nora this morning.
她跟我说你的贝隆夫人音乐派对
She told me about your Evita listening party.
伦敦和纽约的唱碟差别很大呢
The London and New York recordings are so different.
你本应告诉她我们是异性恋的
You were supposed to tell her that we're straight.
她也不相信我啊
She didn't believe me, either.
你现在这么做是给我捣乱
You're doing this to mess with me.
纠正  我刚开始就是给你捣乱
Correction--I started doing this to mess with you.
我现在正努力达成目标
Now I'm honestly trying to hit that.
所以你装成一个和我在一起的
By pretending you're gay
和我有关系的同性恋吗
And in a relationship with me?
我们的关系让我们都不高兴
We're in a relationship and we're really unhappy.
沟通对我们来说从来没容易过
Communication's never been easy for us.
也许因为我们总是不开诚布公
Probably 'cause we're so closeted.
我计划好了
I got it all figured out.
诺拉和我在几星期内会
Nora and I spend the next few weeks
一起出去玩
Hanging out,
成为好姐妹
Become best girlfriends.
我对她坦白我们的关系
I confide in her about our issues.
我不知道你的计划是
I can't decide if this plan
卑鄙呢还是无逻辑
Is more despicable or illogical.
然后有一晚  我们喝醉了
Then, one night, we get drunk...
背部按摩转移到了前面
Back rub turns into a front rub...
第二天早上
The next morning,
我从来没有对女人有这种感觉
"I've never felt this way about a woman before."
你确实很有决心要上
That's...quite a commitment you've made
我想约会的女人
To jumping the girl I'd like to date.
我想跟她约会
I'd like to date her.
意味着我可以重复上她
In the sense that I'd like to jump her repeatedly.
我先见到她的
I saw her first.
什么  你是在引用男人之间的条例吗
Seriously? You're invoking the guy code?
我们是男人啊  而且这是条惯例
We're guys. It's a code.
只有在知道自己要输的时候
You're only bringing this up
你才会把这条提出来
'cause you know you're gonna lose.
不是感染
It's not an infection,
可是有可能是自主神经絮乱症
But it might be an autonomic nerve disorder.
我还是看不惯你的新发型
The hair is still bumping me.
你剪头发
Did you get it cut
是因为你已经准备好翻开新的篇章还是
Because you're ready for the next chapter or--
两次取骨髓的时候针都被卡住了
We stuck a needle into his spinal bodies twice.
心率正常
His heart rate stayed normal.
如果我们把这和其他症状联想起来
If we add that to his other symptoms...
那是不对的
That would be a mistake.
她不会中计的
She's never gonna fall for it.
那你就没什么可担心的啦  亲爱的
Well, then, you got nothing to worry about, sweetie.
你是个懦夫
You're a wuss.
等我好起来的时候才这么说我
Say that when I'm better.
什么啊  你想打我啊
What, are you gonna beat me up?
好怕哦
That sounds stressful.
也许你应该先嗑点贝塔受体阻滞药
Maybe you should pop one of your beta blockers first.
你心脏有问题吗
You have a heart problem?
医学上说  没有
Medically, no.
要有的话他会告诉我们
He would have told us about that.
暗示着
Metaphorically...
是法律以外的事情造成的结果
It's an effect from operating outside of the law.
有时候我得对无辜的人
Sometimes, I have to do bad things.
做坏事
And not always to bad people.
上几个月  我过得不太好
Last few months, that hasn't been so easy.
有个人给了我一些药丸
A guy got me the pills.
它们减轻了我的压力
And they control the stress.
听着  别告诉艾迪好吗
Look, don't-- don't say anything to Eddie. All right?
我最不想见到的事情
The last thing I need
就是他们以为我已经不行了
Is the guys thinking that I've gone soft.
在我们起初接诊你之前
When was your last pill
你最后是什么时候服用过
before we originally admitted you?
那晚之前
Um, the night before.
我们是在这里给你取骨髓的
And we stuck you in here,
你没服用贝塔受体阻滞药
And you went into beta blocker withdrawal.
这导致了高血压
That's what caused the hypertension.
他从这里出去之后  又吃了一片
When he got out of here, he took another pill,
于是高血压症状没有了
And the hypertension went away.
意味着这从来就不是一个症状
Which means it was never a symptom.
排除了这一点
We take that off the table,
我们还有眩晕  发烧的症状
We've got vertigo, fever...
还有紧张
And stress.
他玩这个游戏有段时间了
He's been in this game for a while.
要不就是他最后几个月突然有了良知
Either he grew a conscience over the last few months
或者他产生过量肾上腺素
Or he's producing excess adrenaline.
嗜铬细胞瘤
Pheochromocytoma.
-什么  -这就是希腊语
- What? - It's Greek for,
对好人做坏事会
"You'll be back doing bad things to good people
现世报
In no time."
给他肾上腺做核磁共振
M.R.I. His adrenal glands.
你做得来吧  你不会用枕头闷死他吧
You're okay with that, right? You're not gonna put a pillow over his face?
哇  真好
Oh, great.
电视送来啦
Cable guy came.
詹姆斯
Hi, James.
我们还有些宫爆鸡丁
We've got some kung pao left.
天啊  就这儿
Oh! God. Right there.
我们在野餐  还有喝酒
We're having a picnic... with wine.
给你倒一杯
I'll pour you a glass.
他不喝酒的
He doesn't drink.
那我们再喝多点
Oh. Well, more for us, then.
我想我可以
I think I might...
吃一些
Have a little...
宫爆
Kung pao.
卡迪怎么说
How'd it go with Cuddy?
她说我需要谈判筹码
She told me I needed leverage.
所以我告诉她我有另外一个工作邀请
So...I told her about an offer I had
让我去领导一个在仁爱医院的神经科
To help run the neuro department at mercy.
你真的要跳槽吗
Are you really gonna take the job?
没有其他工作
There is no other job.
我在虚张声势  她回应了
I bluffed. She called it.
我可不要求她涨工资
I'm not gonna beg to be underpaid.
这个病例完了我就离开
I'm leaving when this case is over.
豪斯骗你的
House is lying to you.
我知道
I know.
你也是
And so are you.
现在都2010年了
It's 2010, I mean...
没有人会在意你是同性恋的
You know, nobody cares if you're gay anymore.
我的意思是  你可以出柜
I mean, you don't have to be in the closet.
我不是
I'm not, I...
看看你周围
Look around you.
这真的像是一个
Does this really look like a place
同性恋住的地方吗
Gay men live?
除了那个海报
Apart from the poster.
我们唯一的家具是这些凳子
Those stools are our only furniture.
窗户也没有装饰
There are no window treatments.
我的前男友甚至不知道
Well, my ex-boyfriend didn't even know
什么叫窗户装饰
What window treatments were.
那木匠兄妹乐队唱片是格雷戈的还是你的
Is that Greg's carpenters album or yours?
听着  豪斯讨厌音乐剧和时尚
Look, House hates musicals and fashion
还有蛋白酥皮
And meringue.
他一直在做戏
This whole thing is an act
为了赢得你的信任
Designed to earn your trust...
从而可以跟你上床
In order to sleep with you.
我明白了
I get it.
终于明白了
Finally.
你是在吃醋
You're jealous.
如果你想多和格雷戈在一起
You know, if you want to spend more time with Greg,
你应该直接告诉他啊
You should just tell him.
你错了
You were wrong.
核磁共振显示没有任何嗜铬细胞瘤的迹象
M.R.I. Revealed no sign of a pheochromocytoma,
意味着米奇的紧张
Which means Mickey's stress
只是紧张
Is just stress.
回到眩晕和发烧
We're back to vertigo and fever.
所以环境又变回我们
And environmental is back at the top
清单的首选因素
Of our list of suspects.
我们要缩小可能性的范围
We're trying to narrow down the possibilities.
那个接收器对人工刺激没有回应
That receiver doesn't respond to manual stimulation.
也许你可以脱衣服
Maybe if you took off your shirt.
实际上我采取更奇怪的方式
Actually, I resorted to something more exotic.
我管它叫阅读说明书
I call it reading the instructions.
事实证明如果你把天线
Turns out if you screw the antennae
插进错的插口
Into the wrong sockets,
它是工作不了的
It doesn't actually work.
我们就是在特顿外跟丢米奇的
We lost Mickey just outside Trenton.
本应是要找一个开放频率
It's supposed to search for an open frequency.
那边的建筑大多是建于
Most buildings there were built
1920至1940年间
Between 1920 and 1940.
我们收集了最常见的毒品清单
We're compiling a list of toxins most common--
至少得有一个开放频率
There's got to be at least one open frequency.
我需要跟你朋友说说话
I need a few minutes with your friend.
你想的话可以留下
Or stay if you want.
直肠测试
Rectal exam.
我去看看那些餐厅
I'll check out the cafeteria.
为什么是贝塔受体阻滞药呢
Why the beta blockers?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
安定和阿普唑仑也缓解紧张
Valium and xanax actually reduce stress.
贝塔受体阻滞药只能减少由压力的病症
Beta blockers just control the symptoms of stress.
稳定心跳的速度  缓轻手抖
Keep the heart from racing, hands from shaking,
以及诸如此类的问题
and all those stage fright issues.
所以有些人会在表演的时候把他们带上
That's why some people take them when they perform.
这是什么
What the hell is that?
这是我的窃听器
This is my bug.
而这个
And this...
这个
Um... this...
这个是你的
This is yours.
你居然窃听自己的房间
You bugged your own room?
你是告密吗
Are you...an informant?
告密者会在他第一次发病的时候
An informant would have sold his pals out to us
就出卖他的朋友
at the first sign of a sniffle.
这个人是个条子
This guy...is a cop.
我可没看出这有什么关系
I don't see how this is relevant.
你搞无聊
In the land of no fun,
还真是有一手啊
you got a really sensible piece of property.
让他休息会儿吧
Give him a break.
就算知道了他是卧底
Knowing this guy's an undercover cop
也不能帮助我们治愈他
doesn't get us any closer to curing him.
说的好  知道人们怎么说吗
Good point. You know what they say.
信息不是力量
Information is not power.
-等等  -你的意思是我们该利用
- Wait... - You're saying we should
这一点去胁迫他开口
use the cop thing to force him to talk?
胁迫吗
Force?
我是打算用类似女人的那套怀柔政策
I'm talking about the womanly art of persuasion.
我是说类似女人的
I said womanly.
如果你不想说
If you won't talk to us,
那我们就去找愿意说的人
we'll find someone who will.
你肯定有个上级
I mean, you must have a supervisor,
接头人之类的吧
a...handler.
祝你们好运
Good luck with that.
你们不知道我的真名
You don't know my real name.
也不知道我是当地警察还是州警察
You don't know if I'm local or state,
是FBI还是药品管理局的
F.B.I., D.E.A.
不过随你们了  打电话去问吧
But, by all means, get on the phone.
我明白  这些人行为卑劣
I get it. These guys are lowlifes.
你想把他们从街上清除掉
You want them off the street.
他们不仅仅是卑劣
They're not just lowlifes.
艾迪三周前杀了一名告密者
Eddie killed a snitch three weeks ago.
这是老板的命令
Boss' orders.
这个老板是全国最大的
The boss, he's one of the biggest cocaine importers
可卡因进口商之一
in the entire state.
他打算把买卖扩张至费城
And he wants to expand down to Philly.
明晚他和艾迪将
Tomorrow night, he and Eddie
与一名重要人物会见
are meeting the big fish.
届时警察将会突击逮捕他们
And the cops are gonna bust it.
如果因为你们在这儿逛悠而暴露我的身份
But if you guys get caught poking around there,
那整件事就会被搅黄了
The whole thing gets called off.
你的行为令人钦佩
That's noble,
可你不能将自己的生命置于险境
but you can't put your life at risk.
我已经做了16个月的卧底
I've been undercover for 16 months.
我一直没有回家
I haven't seen my wife...
没见我的妻子和我的狗
my house, my dog.
为此我付出了太多
I have put far too much into this,
我不会让这一切半途而废的
and I will not let it fail.
所以
So just...
只要让我再活24小时就行了
just keep me alive for another 24 hours.
到时我会告诉你们想知道的一切
And I will tell you everything you need to know.
我能进来吗
Uh, can I come in?
护士们一直粘着我
Nurses out here can't keep their hands off of me.
他还真是个花花公子啊
He's a casanova, huh?
那么  你给我带了一份三明治吗
What, you bringing me my sandwich?
没有  因为
No, because, guess what.
我不会读心术
I don't read minds.
你怎么了
You okay?
由于肠系膜上动脉血液凝块
He had a G.I. Infarction caused by a clot
导致的心肌梗死
in his superior mesenteric artery.
我们得切除一段肠
We had to remove a foot of bowel.
如果血栓继续增加
If more clots keep forming,
他可能活不过24小时
he may not last 24 hours.
可那个傻子还不愿开口
And the moron still won't talk.
坏人拉风  好人就是傻子吗
Bad guy, cool; good guy, moron?
差不多
Pretty much.
他可是个英雄
Guy's a hero.
为了把毒贩送进大牢他可冒着生命危险
He's risking his life  to put these dealers in jail.
那些因此而上位的毒贩
I'm sure the dealers who take their places
肯定会对他心存感激
will be very grateful.
那么他的症状是头晕  发热还有血栓
So vertigo, fever, and thrombosis.
我们已经排除了癌症以及感染的可能性
We've already ruled out cancer and infection.
使用类固醇以后  他的病加重了
He got worse on steroids,
那也排除了自身免疫系统问题
which suggests it's not autoimmune.
所以我们就卡在环境因素上了
So we're stuck with environmental.
可究竟是什么环境因素呢
But what kind of environmentals?
毒药  寄生虫还是过敏呢
Toxins, parasites, allergens.
我们应该选出10种可能性最大的疾病
We should just pick the top ten possibilities
-一起治疗  -怕是这么做会
- And treat for all of them. - Except that treating for everything
让他死的更快
could kill him faster than whatever's killing him.
你有更好的想法吗
Got a better idea?
差不多  奇斯说的对
Sort of. Chase is right.
我们的病人为了高尚的事业顽强坚持着
Our patient is holding out for noble reasons:
那就是掩护这次搜查
protecting his bust.
如果这支队伍里的其他人生病了
Anybody else on that crew got sick,
我想他们会更配合我们吧
I'm guessing they'd be a little more self-serving.
谢谢
Thanks.
手术很顺利
Surgery went well.
你一会儿就能看见他了
You'll be able to see him soon.
以前说这么做可以解决儿童睡眠问题
Yeah, used to be all about ferberizing your kid.
现在他们又说这会扰乱他们的睡眠
Now they're saying it could mess them up.
我的孩子六岁半了
My--mine's 6 1/2.
米奇的病情在恶化
Mickey's getting worse.
出现血栓是不好的预兆
The clot is a very bad sign.
请你告诉我们他去过哪里
We really need you to tell us where he's been.
是我做的
I do that...
本来我很可能会
There's a very good chance
在缅因县变成个无名死尸
that I could end up John Doe at the county M.E.
米奇因为过分暴露而染上疾病
Look, Mickey got sick because he had the most exposure.
其他人也有危险
Other guys are at risk too.
你不想
You don't want to...
你没事吧
You okay?
我觉得头晕
I -- I feel dizzy.
你有糖尿病吗
Are you diabetic?
没有
No.
上一次去你的办公室是什么时候
When was the last time you were at your office?
-你是不是给我下药了  -什么
- Whoa...did you drug me? - What?
你想让我觉得我病了
You're trying to make me think that I'm sick
那我就会带你去我们的藏身处
So I'll take you to the stash.
当然不是  如果你病了
Of course not, but if you are sick--
我没病  我感觉被下药了
No, I don't feel sick. I feel drugged!
别想蒙我  我知道两者之间的区别
Trust me, I know the difference.
你一半都没喝完
You didn't even drink half of it.
一小时后你就会没事了
You'll be fine in an hour.
你们觉得米奇会死吗
You think Mickey could die?
好吧  就这么一次
Ah, it's just a deal.
我带你去
I'll take you.
我们在这儿头都抬不起来
Couldn't have given us a heads up
他真的是住在洗衣房吗
that he was living in a drycleaner?
这活生生的就是个毒药缸子
It's like living in a vat of poison.
看完没  我们可以走了吗
Is that it? Can we get out of here?
我得把所有地方都查看一遍
I gotta cover all our bases.
好吧  看那儿
Okay, fine. Look...back there.
快点
Hurry up.
这是什么  是化学药品吗
What are these, more chemicals?
不完全是
Oh, not exactly.
如果这是病因的话
Uh...if this stuff was the problem,
那就不会只有他一个人生病
there'd be a lot more sick people.
你打电话给条子了吗
Did you call the cops?
没有
No.
不应该有人在这儿的啊
No one's supposed to be here.
过来
Come here.
我说了不准吻我
I said no kissing!
艾迪
Eddie.
没想到你在这里啊
I didn't know you'd be here.
听着  我只跟你有交易
Look, the deal was just for you.
这个男人想看的话  你得再付50美元
This guy wants to watch, it's an extra 50.
哥们儿  这是私人聚会
Yeah, private party, man.
今晚我守这儿吧
Uh...I got it covered tonight.
做的不错啊
Nice.
我都快嫉妒死了
The jealousy is... killing me.
那个  显然他在意你
Well...he clearly cares about you.
非常的在意你
Very much.
为什么他就不能正常的表达出来呢
Why can't he show it in a-- in a normal way?
我受够了
I'm so tired of...
他的沉默和对我的忿恨
the whole silence and the resentment.
今晚我都不想回去
I don't know if I can go back there tonight.
我需要一些时间
I need some time.
去我那儿吧
Come stay at my place.
真的吗
Really?
肯定会很有趣的
It'll be fun.
就像那种通宵派对
You know, like a -- like a sleepover.
那将会  那将会
That would -- that would be...
那将会极大的帮助我
It would be such a help.
谢谢你
Thank you.
豪斯
House.
你来这儿干吗
What are you doing here?
我来这儿是因为
I'm here because...
你说什么也无法改变既定的事实
Nothing you can say is going to change anything.
我爱这个男人
I love this man.
我不会再浪费生命的一刻
And I am not wasting another moment
去否认这一切
of my life denying that.
格利高里·豪斯
Gregory House...
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
太意外了
This is unexpected.
快说愿意啊
Say yes!
我该走了
I'm gonna go.
别别  别走
No--no, no, no.
你们显然有话要说
You two obviously have some talking to do.
不好意思
Excuse me.
怎么样了
How's it coming?
目前为止  一无所获
So far, nothing.
地毯  画  隔热材料
Carpet, paint, insulation.
甚至连冰箱里所有的食物都检查了
Even the gross food in the fridge.
都没有异样
Everything's coming up clean.
只剩下干洗剂没有排除
which leaves the dry-cleaning chemicals.
几分钟后出结果
Should have the results in a few minutes.
福曼已经给他用了
Foreman's already started him
吸入式沙丁胺醇
on inhaled albuterol.
有可能这病例已经解决了
Chances are, this case is over.
-我们得告诉他  -不行
- We have to tell him. - We can't tell him.
这改变不了卡迪让他卷铺盖的事实
Won't change the fact that Cuddy let him walk.
只会让他知道
It'll just let him know
这只是一个白痴恶作剧闯的祸
it was all because of a stupid prank.
我们得跟卡迪讲
We have to tell Cuddy.
自首然后求她让他留下
We confess and beg her to take him back.
祈求有用的话  他就该加了薪了
If begging worked, he would have a raise,
我们也不用在这儿焦头烂额的
and we wouldn't be screwed.
沙丁胺醇不起作用
Albuterol is not helping.
病人开始咳血了
Patient started coughing blood.
再加异丙托铵怎么样
What about adding ipratropium?
那就会
That might--
别费那劲了
Don't bother.
本来猜想干洗剂用的是全氯乙烯
We assumed this place was using perchloroethylene.
结果是...石油溶剂
Turns out... petroleum solvents.
毒贩子开了个环保干洗店吗
The drug dealers are running a green drycleaner?
真抱歉拆你这黑色幽默的台
I hate to push past the irony,
但我们的病人现在肺出血
but our patient's bleeding into his lungs,
我们还一无所获
and we've got nothing.
昨晚得到的肺扫描通气-灌注系数
The v/q scan last night
显示存在一个肺动脉瘤
showed a pulmonary aneurysm.
解释了咳血症状
Explains the coughing blood.
我做了栓塞止血
I did an embolization to stop the bleeding,
但他今早又开始咳
He then started up again this morning.
结果出现了另三个动脉瘤
Three more aneurysms.
像是霉菌性动脉瘤
Those look like mycotic aneurysms.
显示有真菌感染
Indicates a fungal infection.
这就和症状切合了
That'd be consistent with his other symptoms:
眩晕  发热
The vertigo, the fever.
我没在那儿看见过霉菌
I didn't see any fungus at the location,
试样也全都--
And none of the samples--
似乎有些人漏掉了什么东西
Looks like somebody missed something.
对有些人来说这真是太丢脸了
which is embarrassing for somebody.
而且  我们给他用的类固醇
And...the steroids we gave him
抑制了免疫系统
would have suppressed his immune system.
如果是真菌  他会有30个动脉瘤
If that was a fungus, he'd have 30 aneurysms.
某些人说得挺在点
Somebody's got a good point.
十二个小时内从一个发展成四个么
One bleed to four in less than 12 hours?
我觉得这表明病情在恶化
That seems like an uptick to me.
趁他还没被自己的血淹死
We need to start him on antifungal meds
得给他上抗真菌药了
before he drowns in his own blood.
用吧
Do it.
过多久起作用呢
How long till it starts working?
几个小时吧
Give it a few hours.
我们会回来检查的
We'll be back to check on you.
来
There you go.
轻松点
Take it easy.
你不该带她去那儿的
You shouldn't have taken her there,
你这白痴
You imbecile.
他们什么都没发现
They found nothing.
你有可能被人爆头的
You could have got your brains blown out.
我必须做点什么
I had to do something.
我不能就这么眼睁睁地看着你...
I couldn't just sit and watch and...
你是我朋友
You're my friend.
谢谢
Thanks.
你也会为我这么做的
You'd do it for me.
我  我得走了
I-I should get going.
费城的大人物今晚到
Got the big man from philly coming in tonight.
你要我留下  我就留下
You want me to stay, I'll stay.
我们知道的吉米全都知道
Jimmy knows everything that we know.
不
No.
我们花在这上面的六个月...
The six months we put in on this...
你得在场
You gotta be there.
明天来看你
I'll swing by tomorrow.
艾迪
Hey, Eddie.
嗯
Yeah?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我没法和你一起去
You know that... I can't go with you.
这都是我们的错
It was all our fault.
我们在作弄福曼
We were screwing with Foreman,
想让他以为自己工资比我们低
Trying to make him think he made less than we did.
显然  事情有些不受控制
Obviously, things got out of control.
好吧  有些人干了些
Well, someone does something
愚蠢又欠考虑的事情
stupid and insensitive,
我总以为是豪斯
I always figure it was house.
真高兴这做得很抢眼
Good to know it's catching.
没有什么第二份工作存在
Look, there is no other job.
他就是想加薪
He was just trying to get a raise.
就算你只多给他一丁点钱
Even if you gave him a little more money,
他都会留下的
I know he'd stay.
我不会只因为你们三个想取乐
I'm not giving Foreman a raise
就加他薪的
because the three of you decided to amuse yourselves.
我们知道  所以
We know, and that's why
多出的钱扣我们的账吧
we want you to take it out of our paychecks.
你们俩没意见吗
You two okay with this?
有其他选择吗
Is there any other option?
没意见
We're okay with it.
福曼是个好组长
Foreman is a good team leader.
他应得的
He deserves it.
那行
Okay, then.
我会这么做的
That is what I will do.
最后说一句
And just so you know...
我不知道你们在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我这三天都没见过福曼
I haven't seen Foreman in three days.
我突然想起那句"谁是你老板"
The phrase "Who's your daddy?" Comes to mind.
来杯咖啡怎么样
Want to grab some coffee?
正窝工呢
Kind of a bad time.
抱歉  你让我顺便来看看  所以
Sorry. Uh, you told me to drop by, so...
我只能这时候来
This is when I could make it.
好吧
Right.
进来吧
Come in, yeah.
威尔森的这整回事
This whole thing with Wilson...
全是我的错
It's all my fault.
我们不是不出柜  我们不是同性恋
We're not closeted, because we're not gay.
真的不是
For real.
威尔森觉得你很可爱
Wilson thought you were cute,
我就是想让他掉链子
And I was just yanking his chain.
这么说可能不太对
Maybe that's not the best phrasing.
所以你和我一起
So you were only spending time with me
只是为了让他搞砸吗
to screw with him?
天  不是
God, no.
我和你一起
I was spending time with you
是因为我想摸你咪咪
because I want to touch your boobs.
贝隆夫人听两次就够了
Enough to listen to Evita, twice.
我讨厌他们讨厌得不行
And I really hate Evita.
你看我多有喜欢你的咪咪
That's how much I like your boobs.
等等  哇哇哇
Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
等一等  等一等
Wait, wait.
威尔森  他是个很好的人
Wilson... He's a really good guy.
他真的很喜欢你
And he really likes you.
好吧  这真是...
Well, it's really...
就你而言这么撑你的朋友还真是不容易
It's sweet of you to stick up for your friend like that.
而你依然试着想和我睡
And you're still trying to sleep with me.
我说不定还会给他电话呢
You know, maybe I will call him.
对你而言不错吧
It would serve you right.
威尔森也是个混蛋
Wilson's a jerk too.
好吧  他至少试着做正确的事
Well, at least he tried to do the right thing.
他离了三次婚
He's been divorced three times.
和快死的病人上床
He slept with a dying patient.
的确他看上去像个童子军
Sure, he looks like a boy scout,
但其实...
But then...
那些动脉瘤
The aneurysms
看上去是霉菌性的  实际不是
Look mycotic, but they're not.
它们是炎症
They're inflammatory.
这不是真菌感染
Because this is not a fungal infection.
高血压是真的症状
The hypertension was a real symptom.
你在误打误撞地
You've been unwittingly
用贝塔阻滞剂治疗
Treating it with beta blockers.
你停药了  血压又回升了
You stopped taking them,and your blood pressure went up
是肺动脉栓塞综合征症
It's hughes-stovin.
好吧  那么怎么...怎么治呢
Okay, so how-- how do we treat this?
没有疗法
We don't.
肺动脉栓塞综合征是自体免疫病
Hughes-stovin is an autoimmune disease.
只要一恶化
Once it's this advanced,
我们就做不了什么了
There's not much we can do.
动脉瘤将持续增殖
The aneurysms keep multiplying.
最终  其中之一将会破裂
Eventually...one of them will rupture.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
要是你在第二天就死掉  我就确定了
If you die in the next day or so, I will be.
即使你把所知的一切都告诉我们
Even if you had told us everything we wanted to know,
也不会有用的
It wouldn't have made a difference.
你做了正确的事情
You did the right thing.
我想通知我的妻子
I think I should call my wife now.
你病人的事  我很遗憾
I'm sorry about your patient.
死时他自认是个英雄
He died a hero in his own mind.
我想这总比一无所有强一些
Guess it's better than nothing.
在电梯里碰见诺拉了
Ran into Nora in the elevator.
她不觉得我们是同性恋了
She no longer thinks we're gay.
现在她觉得我们是骗人的混蛋
Now she thinks we're mendacious dirt bags.
撒谎的混球对我来说更自然些
Mendacious dirt bag comes much more naturally to me.
至少可以把那东西扔掉了
Least we can get rid of that.
我挺喜欢它呢
I kind of like it.
倒是挺讨厌这沙发的
Unlike this sofa.
这可是500美金啊
It's 500 bucks.
还能让你躺着呢
And... it reclines.
*一个*
*One*
*突出的感受*
*Singular sensation*
*她每个轻步*
*Every little step she takes*
我要揍你脸了
I will punch you in the face.
不扔沙发我就不停
I'll stop, if you get rid of the sofa.
不可能
No chance.
*令人兴奋的组合*
*Thrilling combination*
*她的每个动作*
*Every move that she makes*
*一个微笑  突然无人*
*One smile and suddenly nobody else,boom*
*将*
*will, boom*
*做*
*Do, boom boom, boom boom*
*你知若与那人一起  将永不孤独*
*You know you'll never be lonely with you know who*